### Contact

9881403575 avdhootj@gmail.com

# Visa & citizenship

Nationality **Indian** 

System generated resume by foundit

# **Avdhoot Joshi**

deputy general manager Ahmedabad

# **Summary**

Professional with 16 yrs of relevant experience of Techno Commercial with Adani (Natural Resources) and Technical Sales/ Product mgmt / Key acct mgmt/ Dealer mgmt of Const and mining equip with Epiroc (Formerly Atlas Copco), Sandvik, L&T Komatsu

Not a job hopper

# **Experience**

### deputy general manager

Adani Enterprises - Feb 2022 - Present . 2 Yrs 0 Mos.

1038 employees | public | More Details

Energy | Manufacturing | Renewable Energy | Solar |

### key account manager

Epiroc - Apr 2018 - Jan 2022 . 3 Yrs 9 Mos.

10000+ employees | Self/Funded/Govt/Others | More Details

Construction Information Technology Manufacturing Mining

#### Responsibilities

\* Managing Sales and business development through tender and retail sale of following product lines to key accounts (PSU, Cement plants, Institutional customer, Private contractors) directly and thru dealers: \* Blast hole drills (DTH, TH and Rotary) \* Exploration drills (Surface and Underground) \* Underground mining (Hard rock) drills (Development & Production) , loaders and trucks \* Rock drilling tools \* Managing distributor in region to achieve growth in business with sustainable and acceptable profit levels.

### **Manager Sales**

Sandvik Asia - Apr 2011 - Mar 2018 . 6 Yrs 11 Mos.

## **GET**

Larsen & Toubro - Jul 2007 - Feb 2011 . 3 Yrs 6 Mos.

10000+ employees | More Details

Construction | Financial Services | Information Technology | Innovation Management | Manufacturing |

### Education

# Bachelor Of Technology (B.Tech/B.E),

2007 - -

# **Awards & Certifications**

### solution sales

linkedin

becoming head of sales: developing your playbook

linkedin

transitioning to management for salespeople

linkedin

business analytics: sales data

linkedin

running a profitable business: understanding financial ratios

linkedin

networking for sales professionals

linkedin

sales: data-driven sales management

linkedin